[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the correct name for a horse of either sex under the age of one year?", "correct_answer": "Foal", "incorrect_answers": ["Colt", "Yearling", "Mare"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The famous department store Harrods that occupies an entire block is located on which road in London?", "correct_answer": "Brompton Road", "incorrect_answers": ["Abbey Road", "Threadneedle Street", "Fleet Street"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A lion is part of which animal class?", "correct_answer": "Mammalia", "incorrect_answers": ["Amphibia", "Aves", "Arachnida"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The actress who played Toula, Nia Vardalos, cast her husband in the movie My Big Fat Greek Wedding.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The largest consumption of cigarettes belongs to this country.", "correct_answer": "China", "incorrect_answers": ["Brazil", "India", "The US"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first attempts at showing motion using still pictures can be traced to this time period.", "correct_answer": "The Paleolithic era", "incorrect_answers": ["Classical Greece", "17th century France", "The Chu Dynasty (China)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This water body, which is South Americas largest freshwater lake, is the highest commercially navigable lake.", "correct_answer": "Titicaca", "incorrect_answers": ["Nyasa", "Nicaragua", "Michigan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is unusual about the curriculum of St. Helens School in Newbury, Ohio?", "correct_answer": "Unicycling is a mandatory subject.", "incorrect_answers": ["Except for Advanced Placement  classes, all classes are taught in Latin.", "Studying at least four foreign languages is mandatory.", "Although it is a Catholic school, Hebrew is a required subject."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Maryland is well known as a colony of religious tolerance.  It was the first American colony to fully accept practitioners of which religion?", "correct_answer": "Catholics", "incorrect_answers": ["Quakers", "Presbyterians", "Jews"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In terms of ratings, this was the top TV show in the USA for the summer of 2008.", "correct_answer": "Americas Got Talent", "incorrect_answers": ["Fringe", "Dancing With the Stars", "Monk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what European country did the Rough Collie dog breed originate?", "correct_answer": "Scotland", "incorrect_answers": ["Germany", "Ireland", "France"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Saturns moon Titan is the largest natural satellite in our Solar system.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]